Antonio Rodriguez

Guadalajara, Jalisco Mexico antoniorbx1998@gmail.com

Software developer with 2 years of experience, Responsible, with professional ethics, critical analysis, ability to work in a team, with a dynamic and enthusiastic nature, easy to learn, participative and proactive, always oriented towards continuous improvement and innovation, currently I have experience using JavaScript and Python technologies.

EXPERIENCE

Apex Systems, Jalisco Mexico

September 2021 - Now Redux, Css, Git, React, Express, Node, Django, Python, OpenCV, PostgreSQL,Axios

UDG VIRTUAL, Jalisco México

March 2021 - August 2021 JavaScript, Css, Html.

EDUCATION

Centro Universitario de Ciencias Exactas e Ingenierías, Jalisco México—

January 2017 - December 2021 College Degree

Proulex Tepeyac, Jalisco Mexico— Certification

2013 - 2015 Certification

SKILLS

Python, Django, OpenCV
Javascript, Node,React,
Redux,Css, Html
Mysql, PostgreSQL
Git, Docker, Docker-Compose
My GitHub

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English, Intermediate